1. runFeatureFile("Include/features/Poin of Sale Page/GL02-Open List Item.feature")
1. com.gpostlite.website.BrowserUtility.openURL("https://devmini.gpos-efarmasi.com/")
5. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Page Masuk - GPOS Lite/glWelcomeContinue"), element_timeout)
9. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Page Masuk - GPOS Lite/glWelcomePage"), element_timeout)
13. verifyTextPresent("Masuk", false)
1. com.gpostlite.website.LoginPage.validateLoginPageElementPresent()
5. setText(findTestObject("Page Masuk - GPOS Lite/glEmail"), username)
9. setEncryptedText(findTestObject("Page Masuk - GPOS Lite/glPassword"), password)
13. com.gpostlite.website.BrowserUtility.clickButton(findTestObject("Page Masuk - GPOS Lite/glBtn_masuk"), STOP_ON_FAILURE, "Success to login")
1. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Page_Dasbor - GPOS Lite/glDashboardTitle"), element_timeout)
5. com.gpostlite.website.LoginPage.validateDashboardPageElementPresent()
1. com.gpostlite.website.BrowserUtility.clickButton(findTestObject("Page_Dasbor - GPOS Lite/glCloseBtnPopup"), STOP_ON_FAILURE, "Success to Close Popup Image")
1. com.gpostlite.website.BrowserUtility.clickButton(findTestObject("Page_Dasbor - GPOS Lite/glPOS"), STOP_ON_FAILURE, "Success to open Poin of Sale Dashboard")
1. waitForElementVisible(findTestObject("Page_Point Of Sales - GPOS Lite/glPOSDashboard"), element_timeout)
5. verifyTextPresent("Testing Accounting V2 (Aris PKP)", false)
1. com.gpostlite.website.BrowserUtility.clickButton(findTestObject("Page_Point Of Sales - GPOS Lite/glSearchBtn"), STOP_ON_FAILURE, "Success to open list item")
1. verifyElementVisible(findTestObject("Page_Point Of Sales - GPOS Lite/List Item/glModalListItem"), STOP_ON_FAILURE)
5. verifyTextPresent("LIST ITEM", false)